KHOIRONI ARIEF

Lamongan, Jawa Timur 6283870461640

Khoironyarief08@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Fresh Graduate of Informatics Engineering at University of PGRI Ronggolawe Tuban, interested in programming especially web programming, experienced as a freelancer web developer, succeeded in creating websites according to client needs. Enjoys learning new things, especially in the IT and programming fields and wants to become a professional web developer.

EDUCATION

S.kom August 2018 – Now

Universitas PGRI Ronggolawe

Tuban

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Dinas Pendidikan Kabupaten Tuban

February 2021 – March 2021

Magang/ PKL

Membuat sistem informasi administrasi untuk pencatatan surat keluar dan masuk

• Freelance June 2021 – Now

Web Developer

Membuat website sesuai permintaan client, project yang pernah saya buat bisa dilihat di web portofolio saya http://khoirony.github.io

SKILLS

Front End : HTML | CSS | Javascript | Bootstrap

Back End : PHP | MySQL | Codeigniter | Laravel

Others : GIT | MVC | OOP

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Komunitas Seni Rupa Roggolawe

Divisi Publikasi (Desember 2019 – Desember 2020)

Mengelola sosial media organisasi, Melakukan dokumentasi kegiatan, dan membuat desain untuk suatu acara.

Sekretaris (Desember 2020 – Desember 2021)

Melakukan administrasi berupa surat menyurat, membuat proposal, lpj, dll.

• Relawan TIK

Head Of Program and APTIKA (Oktober 2021 – Oktober 2023)

Merancang program atau kegiatan bulanan

PORTOFOLIO

Website : https://khoirony.github.io/
Repositories : https://github.com/khoirony
Design : https://instagram.com/fiktif_b/

LANGUAGES

Indonesia: Native Language

English: Novice Listener, Speaker, and Write. Intermediate Reading